and mothers don’t want to go out and ask
а матери не хотят выйти типа и задать
Putin a question like Putin. Why are our
Путину вопрос типа Путина А за что наши
children dying
дети умирают
there? I’ll say. So for many people this
там я скажу Так что очень многих этот
question has been brewing for a long time, but everyone’s
вопрос уже давно назревает но у всех
hands are tied and no one can
связаны руки и никто не может ничего
do anything because the system has tied their hands so much,
сделать потому что настолько связала
I’m Russian  nationalist
система руки я вот русский националист
Yes, I am, and I can’t do anything unnecessary,
Да я вот а я не могу ничего лишнего
it’s very sad that in our country we are
сделать это очень печально что мы у себя
like trash on Well, that’s how it is
как сорная на Ну так и есть
Hello Hello Oh, you see
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте О вы вижу
some kind of imperial,
какой-то имперец
yes you have this emperor there
да у вас там этот император которого
Bolsheviks Cool yes I'm from the city of
большевики Прикольно да Я из города
Khmelnitsky You're from the Moscow
Хмельницкий Вы откуда я с Московской
region and the
области а
city I abstain apr I understand Well I do
город я воздерживаюсь апре Поня понял Ну
n't know I
не знаю Я
think
дума коро
that's how you feel about the communists who have a
такие вы относитесь коммунистам которые
very negative attitude towards the Tsar Yes, but you did
царя очень негативно Да а вот вы делали
some actions so that Lenin would be
какие-то акции чтобы Ленина короче
taken away from Red Square in short  Yes, we
забрали с Красной площади Да мы
signed petitions and our guys
подписывали петиции и там наши ребята на
went out to picket there.
пикеты выходили Прикольно
Cool Cool. And you’re like, Now you’re in favor of
Прикольно А вы типа Сейчас вы как за
restoring the Russian
восстановление Российской
Empire. No, that’s no longer possible. In any
империи Нет это уже невозможно В любом
case, I’m just  The imperial ideology is very close to me. I
случае я просто очень близка мне
wonder what the
интересно А в чём состоит имперская
imperial ideology is. I’m not very good at imperial
идеология Я не совсем силён в имперских
ideologies. I really like the
идеологиях меня очень нравится как
policy of the empire, which was like the
политика империи которая была как бы и
migration policy at that time, and the
миграционная политика в то время и как
agricultural industry, everything is cool.
агропромышленность всё прикольно А у вас
Who were your ancestors during the
предки кем были при
empire?  Well, I had a
империи Ну у меня был
grandfather, a great-grandfather, he was a white Cossack nsm If
дед прадед был белым казаком нсм Вот бы
only I hadn’t delved into who they were.
а так уже я не углублялся там какие кто
Well, unfortunately people usually don’t talk about four great-grandfathers  I
Ну а про прадедов четверо обычно у людей
know, unfortunately, it’s
к сожалению не знаю к сожалению это
very expensive. That’s all, well, it’s just, well, it
очень дорого Это всё что ну просто ну
turns out, as it were, for the majority. Well, who
получается как бы у большинстве Ну кому
owned the Empire? The Empire
принадлежала Империя Империя
belonged to the emperor. Yes, everyone else
принадлежала император Да все остальные
there was like,
там были это как бы
uh, his subjects, yes, that is, it turns out that
ээ подданные его да то есть получается
your ancestors in this empire didn’t
ваши предки в этой империи ничего не
mean anything, so it turns out I  unfortunately
значили так получается я к сожалению
zala that I don’t know Well, all all the ancestors of
заля что я не знаю Ну так все все предки
all people except if you are not a
всех людей кроме если у вас вы не
Descendant of the Tsar, well, in short, your ancestors in the
Потомок царя да то короче ваши предки в
Empire did not mean anything, yes Well, yes, it’s cool,
Империи ничего не значили да Ну да да
that is, And you like it
прикольно то есть И вам это нравится
politics Well, that’s better anyway  than now
политика Ну это всяко лучше чем сейчас
Well, look now, you are signing some kind of petition,
Ну смотри сейчас Вы какую-то петицию
yes, you are signing petitions, you also signed
да петиции подписываете ещё подписывали
us to remove Lenin, yes, well,
нас чтобы Ленина убрать да да ну
look, under the empire, your ancestors did not
смотрите при империи ваши предки не
have any voice, so why are you
имели никакого голоса да то что ж вы тут
going to elections here, signing petitions,
на выборы ходите петиции подписываете
too, I don’t go to elections Well  in And
тоже я не хожу на выборы Ну во А петиции
why are you signing petitions? There is an emperor, you have
зачем подписываете есть император у вас
this ruler there, he keeps himself
там вот этот правитель само держится
in short. Let him
короче Пусть он
decide. Well, you yourself believe your words
решает Ну сами се верите своим словам
that something is [ __ ] decided, and who
что что что-то решает бля а кто
decides, I don’t know  good And who in
решает то это не зна хорошо А кто в
Russia decides matters,
России решает дела
probably Who specifically is
наверно Кто конкретно
Kolomoisky
коломойский
Chubais Well, no, well, if you look at it like that Yes, it’s
Чубайс Ну нет ну если так посмотреть Да
clear that Vladimir Vladimirovich
понятно что Владимир Владимирович что-то
is trying to do something. [ __ ], you just called him that
там пытается Бля ты прямо его назвал так
Vladimir Vladimirovich by his first name and patronymic
Владимир Владимирович по имени отчеству
cohabitant with trepidation No, I’ll carefully
сожитель трепетом Нет я аккуратненько
just agree on the Internet
просто договорюсь в интернете
not Well  It’s just easy for you to say. You’re
не Ну вам просто легко говорить Вы
probably not from Russia, but I feel like I’ll
наверно не из России а мне как бы я сес
say something wrong to someone in front of me. But I
что-нибудь не так скажу комне при А я
thought you were  imperial and you are like for Putin, no
думал вы имперец и вы типа за Путине не
I don’t support it’s cool the first
я не поддерживаю прикольно первого
imperial is not for Putintsev I met but
имперца не за Путинцев встретил а войну
you support the war against Ukraine
против Украины поддерживаешь
I am against any war I support my
Я против любой войны я поддерживаю своих
guys Who is it with whom I grew up went together
парней Кто там с кем я вместе рос пошл
That is, you support Yes the occupation of
То есть ты поддерживаешь Да оккупацию
Ukraine No I do not support Ukraine  well,
Украины Нет я не поддерживаю Украины ну
wait, I help and support
подожди по я Я помогаю и поддерживаю
my boys, you went there as
своих пацанов ты пошёл туда как пошёл
they went on their own,
они самостоятельно
someone went on their own, someone took someone away, they
пошли кто-то сам кто-то кого-то забрали
raped them, so wait, I didn’t  I understood that
насили Так подожди то я не понял то
Putin sent them or they themselves went,
Путин их отправил или они сами ещё пошли
why did they send someone someone someone
зачем они пошли кого-то кого-то кого-то
Putin sent them So and those who themselves sent
Путин отправил Так а те что сами пош
one there is one who went himself Well, he
один есть один есть кто сам пошёл Ну он
himself went to fight against a Foreign country and
сам пошёл воевать против Чужой страны и
you support him So  you
ты его поддерживаешь Значит ты
support this war
поддерживаешь эту войну
I don’t support
я не поддерживаю
the Slavs Yes but your boys [ __ ] the Slavs
славян Да но твои пацаны Да пошли славян
they Slavs went the
они славяне пошли
Slavs It’s their choice So far in short it’s
Славян Это их выбор Пока короче это
Akhmat strength in short there he saw it as the son of
Ахмат сила короче там видел это как сын
Akhmat the son of this
Ахмата сын этого
Kadyrov  beat up a guy like a Russian and that all
Кадырова избивал типа русского и что все
Russians are
русские
True Well, this is this and it’s very, very
Правда Ну вот это вот это и очень очень
pathetic And that no one can do anything
жалко И что никто ничего не может делать
like that, the question is your boys, instead of
так так вопрос твои пацаны вместо того
putting things in order in their
чтобы короче наводить порядки в своей
country, they go to die Slavs in Ukraine,
стране идут умирать славян в укра
I agree, I’m the only one who left, he said  I do
согласен я Один Он один ушёл сказал мне
n’t seem to have the same enthusiasm as at the
как бы уже такого энтузиазма нет как в
beginning he left, he said I won’t go again
начале он ушёл сказал я больше не поеду
because what kind of Russian world are we bringing
потому что какой мы несём русский мир
if a mosque has already been built in Mariupol, he
если в Мариуполе уже построили мечеть он
says I don’t understand while our guys
говорит я не понимаю пока парни наши там
are getting migrants there  they are
заводят мигрантов которые уничтожают
simply destroying the Russian culture of the wives
просто рускую культуру жен
Rukh of the Russian-speaking even
Рух русскоязычных даже
Slavs BC is very difficult
славян ВС очень сложно
and why do you support these guys And
и зачем ты поддерживаешь этих пацанов А
why should I go against my guys, what should I
что мне проти своих парней пойти что
say guys BC, go tell the boys,
сказать парни ВС идите скажи парни
in short, turn around
короче разворачивайтесь
here
сюда
SV
СВ
with half half of the ses can’t
с половина половина сес не может
pony them up
пони их по
yes Well, look, well  like you
ь да Ну смотри ну типа ты по ты
support the
поддерживаешь
Slavs No, I don’t support s Well
славян Нет я не поддерживаю с Ну как
look, you send your boys
Смотри ты своим пацанам да присылаешь
some money, goods and so on Yes
какие-то деньги товары и так дальше Да
yes  Well, that is, you support you
да ну то есть ты поддерживаешь ты
arm them, you
вооружает им
give them, I tell them that their mothers
даёшь я передаю что матери им
prepared food for them,
подготовили еду
no
не
more than any support for the army is
более любая поддержка армии - это
support for the war. I don’t understand, I’ve been with people
поддержка войны Я не понимаю я с людьми
since birth. And what should I
с рождения был И что мне как бы их
send them this and they ask you? Come on,
послать это а они просят тебя Дава давай
give it to us  that’s all, yes, the mothers don’t ask me because they
передавай нам это всё да меня не просят
ask me because I’m in touch with their mothers,
матери просят пото что я с матерями на
everyone is very
связи все очень
worried. What can I do for my part, I’m a
переживают Я что могу со своей стороны я
hairdresser, I cut the guys’ hair
парикмахер стригу парней ра
and so
и так
on, good, but the mothers don’t want to
далее хорошо а вот а матери не хотят
go out and ask Putin  a question like
выйти типа и задать Путину вопрос типа
Putin And why are our children dying
Путина А за что наши дети умирают
there I will say So for many people this
там я скажу Так что очень у многих этот
question has been brewing for a long time but everyone’s
вопрос уже давно назревает но у всех
hands are tied no one can do anything
связаны руки никто не может чего сделать
because the system has tied their hands so much
потому что настолько связала система
I’m a Russian nationalist Yes I am and I
руки я вот русский националист Да я а я
can’t do anything more  I did it right away.
не могу ничего лиш сдела пото сразу
It’s very sad that in our country we are
Вот это очень печально что мы у себя в
like second-rate people. Well, it is. Well, it’s
как второсортная на Ну так и есть Ну
clear. Yes, this is all they control
понятно Да вот эта вся они управляют
us and they achieved this, they started a
нами и они добились этого развязали
war. Yes, but more than that they staged the genocide of the Russians.
войну Да но больше геноцид русских
Yes, but look  at the same
устроили Да но смотри в тоже в то же
time, your friend who kind of went
время твой знакомый который типа пошёл
to war against Ukraine, he is also a Russian
на войну против Украины он тоже русский
nationalist. As I understand it,
националист Я так понимаю
how many Russian nationalists are fighting
Сколько русских националистов воюет
against Ukraine, they deliberately went to the
против Украины поехали сознательно на
Donbass, there are all sorts of Russians SMU
Донбасс там всякие Русичи СМУ
Yes, I know, well, let’s go,
Да знаю Ну поехали
many Russians Well, the idea is
да многи русские Ну идея
to protect the LPR And what what  that's not the case with the
лднр защитить А что что не так с
ldnr they were subjected to the russians there. People
лднр подвергались с там русских Люде
how much Ukraine destroyed people in the
сколько Украина уничтожила людей в
ldnr they fired at how many they found there
лднр обстреливали сколько там обрели
because the war started because you are
потому что война началась потому что вы
in  than a year troops were led into the Crimea in the Donetsk
в чем году вели войска в Крым в донецкую
Lugansk region Well, this means that they had to
луганскую область Ну это значит что надо
bomb houses because the war was on
было бомбить дома так война была по
ours, they were shooting at us, they were shooting at us. Well,
нашим стреляли наши стреляли Ну
of course, it’s not a dispute
конечно не спор
to anyone at all, he didn’t shoot at all,
к никого вобще не
or what do you think, for example,
стрелял или как Как ты думаешь например
that they just drove up Ukraine govo Let
что просто подъехали Украина гово Давай
’s go there  somewhere in the house Shots Here are the
мы вот туда где-то в дом Выстрели Вот
guys from Kharkov on a tank Well, it’s clear
ребята с Харькова на танке Ну понятно
that no
что нет
[music]
[музыка]
no, well, the guys’ idea Yes, protect the Russian
нет ну идея парней Да защитить русских
people Novosi, wait, I understand correctly
людей Новоси подожди я правильно понимаю
that you understand  that you can’t
что вы понимаете что вы не можете
protect Russians in Russia Daro
защитить русских в России Даро
son, how much strength this crane has, was just
сын какме сил этого журавля просто
demonstratively showing you can’t
показательно выставлял вы не можете
protect Russian people in
защитить русских людей в
Russia, you’re going to protect Russian people
России едете защитить русских людей
somewhere in Ukraine, I agree, this is
где-то в Украине это я согласен Это
funny, I don’t understand this myself, why is
смешно Это я сам этого не понимаю почему
this so, it’s just a laugh  Well, that’s it, I
так это просто ржака Ну это это я
agree, first you need to figure yourself out,
согласен сначала надо себя разобраться
then you climb somewhere, it’s not happening,
потом куда-то лез ни это не происходит
there’s a lot of money everywhere, it’s us, Ordinary
там огромные деньги везде это мы Обычные
people like that can’t, that’s ordinary, it’s
такие люди не можем та обычные это у вас
in your heads, look, a bunch of Russian
в головах смотри куча российских
nationalists have gone  to fight against
националистов поехали воевать против
Ukraine for some kind of ldnr yes A bunch and
Украины за какой-то там лднр да Куча и
your friend also turns out
твой вот знакомый получается тоже
deliberately Went Yes and a bunch of them
сознательно Пошёл Да и куча таких потому
because they have no brains and Akhmat that Akhmat
что в мозгах у них нет а Ахмат что Ахмат
makes money from this
на этом набивает
and moreover, you saw this
деньги да более того ты видел эти
news Yes, like in the Lugansk region
новости Да как в Луганской области
how many
сколько
Akhmatovs have made these Russian girls
Ахматов сделали русских этих девушек
who live in
которые живут в
Lugansk
Луганске
with This is very sad I hate them with all my
с Это очень печально их ненавижу всей
heart many
душой многи
guys and what do you understand you hate you
ребята и что понимаешь ты ненавидишь ты
guys also hate but In short  let's
пацаны также ненавидят но Короче поехали
damn go die in Ukraine for
блин умереть в Украину
volunteers I didn't go, I decided that I
добровольцам Я не поехал я решил что я
would be more useful here, I stayed here What
тут буду полезнее я остался тут Чем
maybe they need to drip on the brains, which is
может может им нужно капать на мозги что
shorter damn guys Let's solve
короче блин пацаны Давайте может решать
our problems in Russia I'm already saying one
в в России наши проблемы Я говорю один
already, I'm already saying one already, well, I went back
уже говорю один уже вот ну уехал обратно
what am I saying, he understood, he didn’t understand that there is
что я говорю он понял он не понял что
no Russian World, it’s
никакого русского Мира нету это
all just the guys who are conscripts who came back,
всё один вернулся ребята которые
that they just told them to
срочники что они их просто их сказали на
go to the Crimea for training, and in the end they put them
учение едем в Крым а в итоге ставили
under Well, they wrote it down, Well, they signed the contract, yes
под Ну записали Ну контракт подписали да
and that’s all And in the end they are there And now even
и всё И в итоге они там А сейчас даже
if deserters are
если дезертиры
recruited by the Turks, they are already constantly
тюр вербуют уже постоянно штурмовиками
being sent to
уже отправляют на
death by stormtroopers And already
смерть Т уже
[music]
[музыка]
Boshi of
боши
any advancements are not really normal
яких продвижений толком нормальных
How can you fight if you
не Как можно воевать если ты сам этого
don’t want it yourself What can you achieve
не хочешь Какие можно достигать
[music] the
[музыка]
result ru climb  to fight in Ukraine
результату ру лезут воевать в Украине
to protect Russian-speaking people there in Odessa in
защищать там русскоязычных в Одессе в
Donetsk in Lugansk if it can be stupid
Донецке в Луганске если может зать тупо
in Moscow in
в Москве в
Moscow Yes  us We want, we have been striving
Москве Да у нас Мы хотим мы добиваемся
for so long for a Russian
уже сколько чтобы нам открыли Русский
cultural center to be opened in Moscow, there is simply no culture,
центр культуры в Москве просто культуры
there is no Russian cultural center. But the
нету русского центра культуры Зато
Tajik diaspora in Moscow,
таджико диаспоре в тре Моск
look, you understand that something is
го смотрите Вы понимаете что что-то не
wrong and you are still going to fight like in
так и всё равно едете воевать как в
Ukraine. Well, that’s what I have  Well, I’m not going anywhere
Украину Ну вот это у меня ну я никуда не
Well, those are those Yes, what are
Ну вот те Да что там
friends, he’s back alone now, he’s currently
друзья вернулся один сейчас он сейчас
undergoing rehabilitation, he lost his leg,
проходит реабилитацию лишился ноги
a boy younger than me, 18 years old,
парнишка младше меня 18 лет
and here’s what he says, for example,
ему а вот что что он говорит например
who’s to blame for what he has  now there is no
кто виноват в том что у него теперь нет
leg,
ноги
he says the Sun will leave early, the Sun will still drag him
говорит ВС рано поедет ВС равно его у
into the with there, he lost his leg without
затяну в с есть он лишился ноги не
understanding why you are and everything will go there
понимая за что выт и всё поедет туда Да
No, well, he has his own attitudes, in any
не ну свои у него установки есть в любом
case, in his head he thinks
случае в голове он считает
[music]
[музыка]
that And you are not for him  you try to say that I serve
что А ты ему не пробуешь сказать что слу
you to go without a leg, in short, why did they
тебе ехать еже без ноги короче ради чего
wait there? Yes, he came when he
за ждали это да он приезжал когда он
says bro. I understand all this, but
говорит братан Я всё это понимаю но уже
how much time has passed; everyone there
сколько времени прошло у меня там все
has become like family. I can’t anymore. It’s just an
стали как семья Я не могу уже Просто
elementary thing to let the guys down there.  already at the
элементарно там парней подвести уже в
beginning it was necessary to say all this
начале надо было это всё говорить
Wait, wait, I don’t understand again, were
Подожди подожди я ещё раз не понимаю то
they forced, were they deceived by everything, or are
их заставили их обманули всё или это там
they there as a family, these are completely different things
они как семья это совсем разные вещи
if As a family, about voluntarily, if he
если Как семья о добровольно если он
understands that theirs, then on the contrary, he will
понимает что ихт то он наоборот будет
zigzag as short as he can Well  if he
петлять короче как может Ну если бы он
understood that, of course, he wouldn’t go as if he were
понимал что конечно не поехал как бы
his own. Listen, again, I can’t get my head
ну свои Слушай опять же я в голову не
around the forester, I have my own idea, especially he’s been
могу за лесником своя есть идея особенно
fighting there for several years now.
уже уже не первый год воюет там
Therefore, I don’t want this to be a sore
Поэтому не хочу это больная
subject. I just don’t understand at all how to
тема Просто я вообще не понимаю как это
understand what’s in Russia  you there, these are so
понимать что в России ти там же этих так
funny, yes, the Roch Nazis of Russia are being persecuted and
смешно да рох нацистов России преследуют
imprisoned,
садят
in short, there you have
короче там вот у вас
this fighter, this Max Divnich, so
это боец этот Макс дивнич так
the axis
ось
together, he was something like Said something against there, a
вме он что-то типа был Сказал против там
mosque somewhere on some lakes,
что-то мечеть где-то на озёрах каких-то
they went against it, they recaptured it  place they wanted to
ходили против отбили это место хотели
build a huge mosque on SM
построить огромную мечеть на СМ
Lake for more than a week they were
озере больше недели вообще находились
there, they didn’t allow anything to be done, thank God
там не давали ничего делать слава Богу
they canceled it and like all these
отменили её и типа все эти типа
Chechen MMA fighters are immediately so against,
Чеченские бойцы MMA сразу такие против
in short, divas that everyone is like that everything  he is the
короче див что все такие там всё он
number one enemy among the Islamic world of
номер один враг среди исламского мира
Russia, number one Well, it’s like, well, we are
России номер один Ну мы как бы вот ну мы
together, we have our own unity, as
вот вместе у нас своё единение есть как
if glorifying, but look, here’s an interesting
бы славя а вот смотри вот интересный
question. Do you think Russia should
вопрос Ты как считаешь Россия должна
be like this Federation, with
быть как вот Федерация вот эта Да с
different peoples, or Russia?  It should
разными народами или Россия Должна
only stay there, for example, the Moscow
остаться только там например Московская
Kalou region Where Russians
калу область Где Вот там русские
historically
исторически
lived there. I think that I think that it is necessary that we
жили Я считаю что я считаю что нужно что
just need to send the CIS countries.
надо просто страны СНГ
Well, like all these Central Asia, all the
послать Ну как всё эти средне Азию всех
people who lived in  not so
как бы ну народа которые жили у не так
wait But you have citizens Okay,
подожди Так у вас же есть граждане Ладно
we’ll put the Uzbeks and Kazakhs out of brackets
мы вынесем за скобки там узбеков казахов
there who live in their own countries But
там которые живут в своих странах А вот
you have the inhabitants of Dagestan Tatarstan
у вас наме жители Дагестана Татарстана
Bashkartastan They’re coming Well, no
башкартастан Вот они приезжают Ну как бы
matter what I think that’s the same Well, what about
нет Я считаю что ну это же Ну а что с
them  Desh, they always lived in Russia
ними Деш они очень всегда жили в России
Like how regi No, well, it turns out,
Как как реги Не ну да ту получается
look Well, if they want to build a
смотри Ну если они хотят построить
mosque in
мечеть в
Moscow Well, no no, I will be against it
Москве Ну нет нет я буду против этого А
Why against it Well  look, if these are citizen
почему против Ну смотри если это граж
regions and there are regions of their own where they
регионы а сво свои есть регионы где они
can do this, wait, that is, look,
могут это делать Подожди то есть смотри
it’s interesting that the Russians can
вот интересно русские могут в
build a church in Bashkortostan Yes, but the
Башкортостане церковь построить Да а
Bashkort there and others can’t build it
башкорт там и другие не могут построить
in Moscow, unless you’re planning on something
в Москве разве мечите в чём то
Well, first of all, broadcast  already Everything is just
Да ну во-первых в вещать уже Всё просто
Moscowabad, well, look again, not if
москвабад ну так смотри ещё раз не если
These are your citizens, yes. That is, you just, I
Это ваши граждане да То есть вы просто я
can’t, how is it being done in your head at the same time,
не могу как у вас в голове одновременно
uh, and now we want without  uh
ээ делается и вот мы хотим без ээ
non-Russians Yes, and we want an Empire like that
нерусских Да и мы хотим Империю типа вот
there, together with the Russians and other peoples.
там вместе с рус с другими народами
We want we want there to be no migration from
Хотим мы хотим чтобы не было миграции
this
вот этой
incomprehensible Central Asian Well, look
непонятной среднеазиатской Ну как Смотри
E,
Е
as if they are not in principle, well,
как бы они не в принципе ну как вот
look, if Dagestan, for example, is
смотри если Дагестан например так
migration from Dagestan to Moscow  it goes like
миграция из Дагестана в Москву идёт так
this, it’s in the middle of your state, and that’s
это в середине вашего государство да то
what it turns out to be: migrants from
Вот что тобто получается мигрантов из
Dagestan Well, not migrants, but migrants
Дагестана Ну не мигрантов а переселенцев
from Dagestan to Moscow, the norm. But for
из Дагестана в Москвы норм А уже
example, from  Azerbaijan is not the norm, yes Well,
например из Азербайджана не норм да Ну
after all, more if you look at the historical part, it’s
всё-таки больше если исторической часть
like Dagestan is still there,
смотреть как бы Дагестана всё-таки там
and the Tsar was like all this
да и царе был как бы всё вот это
and And like, where was Uzbekistan,
и А как бы где был Узбекистан
Tajikistan, this is the
Таджикистан это
Armed Forces on Kazakhstan? Yes, Kazakhstan and
ВС на Казахстан Да что Казахстан что
Dagestan, approximately In alone there
Дагестан приблизительно В одни там
periods Yes,
периоды Да был
well, well, no matter what, we’re talking now It would still be going on,
ну ну как бы нет го речь сейчас Ещё идёт
well, now it would be more the biggest
бы ну сейчас бы больше самая большая
problem is the migration of
проблема это вот миграция
the SZI with its indigenous peoples,
сзи со своими коренными народами
it’s Look, I don’t understand, for example, what’s the
это Смотри я не понимаю например чем
difference that will come  an Armenian to Moscow
разница что приедет армянин в Москву да
and a Dagestani there, a Tabasaran to
и дагестанец там вот там табасаранец в
Moscow. Both of them at about the same
Москву И те и те приблизительно в одно
time ended up in the Russian Empire,
время попали в Российскую империю
let’s say Well, yes, well, I look against it in
допустим Ну да Ну я я на смотрю против
general, I would remove him, he’s not warm at all,
вообще я бы его убрал меня он вообще не
not cold. I think that he’s just  there
тепло не холо Я считаю что он просто там
it’s like a tumor you I think who
он это как опухоли вы Я считаю кто
Dagestan is not good but Yakutia
Дагестан нет хорошо а а Якутию оставили
would be left in Russia Yakutia would be left So
бы в России Якутию бы оставили Так
wait stop That is, it turns out
подожди стоп То есть получается
you don’t like the Dagestanis Well, I don’t
дагестанцы тебе не нравятся Ну вот я не
I can understand the logic in the World Cup because everything
могу понять в ЧМ логику потому что всё
is connected with crime and connected with
связано с преступностью и связано с
influence about the Yakuts, where I don’t see them at all,
влиянием про якутов где вообще их не
even if they exist, they are very
вижу даже если они есть то они очень
respectful.  for
уважительно Поня то есть ещё раз смотри
example, yes,
типа не борцухи не бахи да например да
like that. And let them be with us, like we
типа то А пусть они будут у нас типа мы
will pull resources from their regions, and
будем из ихних регио тянуть ресурсы а
we pull resources from Dagestan, they smoke us,
Дагестан мы тянем ресурсы они нас курят
that they come in large numbers to
что они приезжают в большом количестве в
Moscow and even there  they build their own order, so it
Москву да и там порядки свои строят так
turns out Well, they are just very strong and
получается Ну они просто очень сильно и
Well, they are all just criminals Well, as
Ну это просто преступники все Ну как все
you all say now, that all the people are
ты говоришь сейчас что весь народ
criminals, so you can say.
преступники наве так можно сказать
There are also people who are criminals
Вот там же есть люди которые преступники
and there are those who are normal, just like
а есть которые нормальные также как и
among the
среди
Russians. Yes, but normal people  They don’t
русских Да но нормальные люди Они не
go to Moscow, that’s what they
едут в Москву вот для того что они
do here, normal people stay at
делают тут нормальные люди остаются у
home at home there again, and Russians
себя дома у себя там ещё раз а русские
sit only in those cities in which they
сидят только в тех городах в которых они
were born, no, no, I speak for the majority.
родились нет нет же за большинство
No, well, Russians travel from different
говорю Не ну русские едут из разных
regions to  Are they going to Moscow or not? Well,
регионов в Москву или нет едут Ну так а
what about when the Dagestanis go, what does it make you
что когда дагестанцы едут что тебя это
nervous then? If a Russian from Kaluga is
тогда нервничает если русский из Калуги
traveling normally and from Vladivostok is
едет нормально и с Владивостока
normal, but from Dagestan Well, there is
нормально а с Дагестана
hostility Well, that’s Well, that is, it
неприязни Ну так это Ну то есть это ты
turns out that you Well, you have some kind of
получается Ну у тебя есть какие-то там
definite hostility  Nazi me and
неприязни определённой наци меня и у
many like-minded people yes yes Well
многих единомышленников да да Ну так
look it turns out well You don’t
хорошо так смотри получается Вы не
like some nations there but you want
любите там какие-то нации но хотите
them to live in Russia I don’t want A
чтобы они жили в России я не хочу А
Yakutia Tatarstan Bashkartastan you have
Якутия Татарстан башкартастан у тебя
no questions good Tatarstan
вопросов нет хорошо Татарстан
Bashkartastan
башкартастан
that I was recently in Kazan a wonderful
что я был недавно в Казани прекрасное
place there where it’s better
место там где вот там получше
than in Moscow you can say there’s no
чем в Москве можно сказать там нет хотя
such thing there at least there’s one mosque there is an
бы такого там там один мечети храма
Orthodox church Well, don’t look again then
православные Ну вот не ещё раз смотри то
Tatarstan you’d like  so that he stays in
Татарстан ты хотел бы чтобы он остался в
Russia Dagestan, I understand you don’t want it,
России Дагестан я понял ты не хочешь да
but
а
Tatarstan actually doesn’t. I would
Татарстан на самом деле нет Я бы их
remove them all. I mean you removed them or
убрал все В смысле ты их убрал или
disconnected them  as if yes because A is
отсоединили как бы да потому что А
good And for example, if for example Russia
хорошо А например если например Россия
were like a Russian republic, it would be
бы вот как русская республика бы да
created within the borders of which regions do you
создалась в границах каких областей ты
see the Russian
видишь русскую
Republic
Республику
[music]
[музыка]
Well, well, listen, I didn’t think about it to
Ну ну слушай я про это не думал чтобы
make just a Russian Republic No,
сделать просто русскую Республику Не ну
well, look if  there Dagestan
как ну смотри если там Дагестан
to secede you don’t want them Tatars
отсоединиться вы не хотите их татары
you don’t want them where that’s where
вы их не хотите куда вот где должна
those areas that you
остаться вот те области которые ты
want should remain for example
хочешь например
well well it won’t be Russia anymore you understand
ну ну это уже будет не Россия понимаешь
either If you look at it like this it’s not
тоже Если так посмотреть это уже тоже не
Russia anymore Well then  because look,
Россия Ну тогда потому что смотри вы
if you take an Empire with different peoples,
если берёте Империю с разными народами
then these peoples live in your
да то тогда эти народы живут в вашей
country And they come to the capital of the
стране Да и они приезжают и в столицу
Empire Yes And you want you want to have
империи Да А вы хотите вы хотите иметь
an Empire with these peoples from them to
Империю с этими народами из них соки в в
Moscow but so that they don’t go to Moscow  did you
Москву но чтобы они в Москву не
come yes no you are coming You are not you are
приезжали да нет вы приезжаете Вы не вы
not there our guys don’t download our guys there for
не там парней наших не качайте там за
your Islam we have like yes wait stop
свой Ислам у нас как бы да подожди стоп
Islam is not their Islam is Russian
Ислам это не их Ислам это российский
Islam Well you officially have Russia yes
Ислам Ну у вас официально Россия да у
you have  no, that you have an Orthodox religion,
вас нету что у вас православная религия
you have and Buddhists live Yes, the Buryats
у вас есть и буддисты живут Да буряты
Kalmyks
калмыки
Arats Puti said or that in fact
араты пути сказал или что по факту у
you have a fafa
вас фафа
country of one nation, for example, like
страна одной нации например как вот там
Poland, yes
Польша да
it is there, the Polish Republic of Russia
это есть там Польская республика Россия
is a Federation of completely
- это Федерация абсолютно
different nationalities Yes subject That is  It’s
разных народности Да субъекта То есть
just that in your head, I see
просто в твоей голове вот я смотрю
it gets along, you want to simultaneously have
уживается ты хочешь одновременно иметь
Russia within such borders and with these
Россию в таких границах да с этими
peoples and And on the other hand, you are
народами и И тебе с другой стороны тебе
unpleasant about the order of these
неприятны порядки этих
peoples, they are creating this chaos,
народов творят это беспредел
why  I say the same mosque, why is
почеме я гово та же самая мечеть почему
it that you were in Kazan, you say there
то что ты был в Казани говоришь в Казани
are churches in Kazan Of course, there are, of course, many
есть церкви Конечно есть конечно много
churches in Kazan, yes, why do
церквей в Казани да да то почему в
you think it’s normal to have Orthodox churches in Kazan,
Казани церкви православной ты считаешь
and when Muslims want to
нормально а когда мусульмане хотят
build a mosque in
мечеть сделать в
Moscow Well, Kazan, in principle, is
Москве Ну Казань в принципе это
Muslim  the region surprised you
мусульманский регион теб удив
because Russia was originally an
потому что Россия изначально
Orthodox country, that’s why there
православная страна я вот за это при
was Orthodoxy during the empire, in any case,
империи было православие в любом случае
go again again, that is, look at
поди ещё раз ещё раз то есть смотри
Tatarstan - this is the place where
Татарстан - это место где и поко веков
the Tatars have lived for centuries, this is their ethnic
проживали татары это ихняя этническая
territory. Yes, they had their own
территория Да вот у них там были свои
customs there. Russia brought churches there not
порядки туда Россия принесла церкви не
so long ago, if we can look. Yes, but
так давно если можем смотреть Да но
they are not like
они не
that, but look,
так но смотри
Russian. They can build a church in
русский Может поставить церковь в
Tatarstan. And when a Tatar wants a church
Татарстане А когда татарин хочет церковь
in Moscow, it makes you feel  some kind of
в Москве это у тебя вызывает какой-то
amazement Well, in Dagestan, for example, there are a
изумление Ну в Дагестане например очень
lot of people who are against churches, for example, there are a
много кто против церквей например
lot of ours, there were a lot of them there recently,
наших очень много сколько там недавно
there was a case when a
вот случай был когда
temple and why did they want Prim they wanted a
храм а и почему а хотели Прим хотели что
mosque, which businessman wanted  to
мечеть кий предприниматель хотел это
open it, who doesn’t even live in Russia.
сделать открыть который даже не в России
That is, he wanted to open it, as it were, but not
живёт То есть это хотел открыть как бы а
only was there supposed to be a
мало того что там должна была быть
mosque there. There should have been a
мечеть Там должно там был там был
huge complex there, there was a madras mosque there,
огромный комплекс там мечеть мадраса
like there was this hospital, a hotel, there was a
типа там этот лечебница гостиница там
shopping center, yes. Well, I still don’t  I
торговый центр да Ну я всё равно не
understand Well, let’s say why, for example,
понимаю Ну вот скажем Почему например
Moscow can, for example, open a
э Москва может например открывать
church there in Ukraine in the territory of
церковь там в Украине в на территории
Russia there in Chuvashia in Bashkortostan,
России там в Чувашии в Башкортостане са
and when these same peoples want to open their own
а когда эти же народы хотят открыть свою
religious building in Moscow, it’s like
культовое сооружение в Москве это типа
Moscow  and you’re not a native Muscovite, as
москви причём Ты же не коренной Москвич
I understand it, yes, a native one. No, you
Я так понимаю да коренной какре Не ну ты
said Grandfather, like a Don Cossack. Well,
сказал Дед типа Донской казак Ну
yes, that is, your parents
да да то есть твои родители где-то
came to Moscow somewhere, for example, they didn’t give birth
приехали в Москву например так не родили
here, they were born. Well, grandparents
тут родились Ну бабушка с дедушкой
came to Moscow. Grandma is not Grandma
приехали в Москву бабушка не Бабушка
either.  I was born here and then it’s good,
тоже тут родилась е дальше хоро
well, someone wasn’t born in Moscow, yes Well, yes,
ну кто-то ж не родился в Москве да Ну да
obviously. That is, it
явно То есть
turns out that you came from some region.
получается ты с какого-то региона
Yes, and you can, like,
приехал Да и ты можешь в Москве типа
make a church in Moscow, yes. For example
делать церковь да А например
Some of these Muslims can’t have a
кто-то из этих из мусульман не может
mosque. Just maybe. Why can I mean that, for
мечеть Просто может Почему может я к
example, we have it on
тому что вот например вот у нас есть на
Butovo? Yes, this is an area just there, well,
Бутово Да вот это район просто там ну
there is a separate taco in Moscow. There’s one
там есть отдельно тако в Москве Там один
very influential Muslim there who is trying
вот мусульманин очень влиятельный добива
to open a full-fledged mosque.  he’s been
чтобы открыть мечеть полноценную он уже
there for about 5 years, he’s been
там где-то на протяжении 5 лет всё там
making agreements on buying land, and so on
договаривался земли покупал и так далее
and so forth Yes, no problem, but he’s
и тому подобное Да без проблем но он это
here, and here is the Earth first. This is the
сде а тут Земля во-первых Вот это Святое
Holy Lake. Well, why is it holy? By the way, I
озеро Ну а чем оно святое Кстати я это
didn’t understand that, well  there  according to the legends of the church,
что не понял ну там по преданиям церкви
according to the legends of the church, everything is just Prita, I
по преданиям церкви всё только прита я
thought there was some kind of church there, a hundred No, there
думал там какая-то церковь сто Нет там
was a church there for real, for real,
была церковь по-настоящему настоящему
just
просто там
in every
в каждом
legend there is a
предание крест
huge cross. What do you think? Let’s finally
огром Как ты думаешь Давай напоследок
How do you think how the war between
Как ты думаешь чем закончится война
Russia and
России с
Ukraine will end? I don’t think it will
Украиной Я считаю она не
will end without ending Well, I think
закончится как не закончится Ну я считаю
that this is a conflict that may subside and
что это конфликт который может утиха а
then again
потом опять
[music]
[музыка]
we will not have a change of
будет у нас не сменятся
power again. What does our
власть так ещё раз Причём тут у нас
power have to do with it? Well, we have replaced Poroshenko
власть Ну у нас вот сменилось Порошенко
with Zelensky  changed and that you too Everything
на Зеленского поменял и что вас тоже Всё
is not good, wait again so the war is not
нехорошо подожди ещё раз так война не
because we have power, some kind of
из-за того что у нас власть какая-то
war is because you attacked us,
война из-за того что вы напали на нас
yes, this is not a dispute Well then, what does it
это да это не спор Ну так А причём тут
matter what kind of power we have?  if you
какая разница какая власть у нас если вы
all are at least we will not
всё ми минимум как минимум у нас не
change Well, that is, ours has something to do with
сменится Ну вот то есть наша при
it
чём-то
Well, at least what about this
ну Ну как минимум что вот про такое
attitude towards the LDPR is
отношение к лдн
not clear And what is the attitude of the NPR not of the LDPR
наме сно А какое отношение кпер не лднр
but of the Donetsk and Lugansk regions
а Донецкой и Луганской области
Ukraine Novorossi and you’re still from the concept of
Украины новоросси а т ты ещё из концепт
Novorossiya not so What is it you
новороссии не так Это же что это ты
think it’s Novorossiya well they lived There the
считаешь это новороссия ну жили Там
first ones were there the
первые там были там
Russians liberated them from and when these
русские освободили от и когда этих этих
all of them were there and settled why they’re not there
всех там был и заселили почему там нет
let’s do that And why then exactly in
давай так А почему тогда вот именно в
these  regions Western turns out to be
этих регионах Западная получается
Ukraine, why then why then are there
Украина почему тогда почему тогда там
so many Russian-speaking people there because
столько вот русскоговорящих людей потому
under the Soviet Union Yes, they brought in a
что При Советском Союзе Да на навели
bunch of workers Yes to these cities Yes villages in the
рабочих куча Да в эти в города Да сёла в
Lugansk region even in the Donetsk region  they
Луганской области ещё в Донецкой области
spoke
говорили
Ukrainian, look at photos like the
по-украински посмотри фотографии типа
thirties and twenties
тридцатых годов двадцатых годов
on the moros, soon the Chechens from Akhmat
на морос ва скоро чеченцы из Ахмата
will be in Moscow Damn, in short, you’re
будут в Москве Блин короче ты наворот
thinking some kind of bloat,
какой-то думаешь
I’m just for ours, in any case, I kind of
Просто я за наших в любом случае я как
said, in short, okay, I’m still waiting, look, I’m
сказал короче ладно я всё жду я смотри я
still waiting  when one of the Chechens and
всё жду когда кто-то из чеченцев Да
publicly some Russian nationalist you
публично какого-то русского националиста
know like that in Moscow. I want to
вот так в Москве знаешь Я хочу
see how Russian nationalists
посмотреть как русские националисты
will continue to remain silent because you  really, here we have nationalists Yes, if anything stood up there against Yanukovych against you, nationalists Well, there’s nothing in Moscow there is there is what question do you have at the next level and at the legislative level it’s prohibited again Well, you have a bunch of a bunch of clubs I I don’t know, a lot Yes, in short, look, in general, okay, we talked, we talked, I’ll say So I’ve always been interested in meeting a Russian nationalist to talk to him Yes, I thought they were there for Rus', in short, for Rus' But really
Будут дальше молчать пото что вы реально
Damn, Russian nationalists have become
блин русские националисты стали
something like that Yes, in Russia we simply
какими-то такими Да в России просто мы
can’t do anything But they dream of
ничего не можем Но зато мечтают о
some kind of historical thing for you SRO Mosk
какой-то мто историче ми вас СРО Моск
no,
нет-то
Novoro
Новоро
they discussed the finals just for themselves
обсуждали финали просто для себя
I don’t understand why we are
пози не понимаю почему мы не разобрав
going somewhere without understanding ourselves  I’m a stranger to me Why is
себя лезем куда-то я для меня чуж Зачем
everything come on Lano everything is
всё давай Лано всё
fine, we
хороше вот мы
saw
увидели
the hijacking, he understands that this is what their Akhmat
угона понимает вот это что там их Ахмат
BN
БН
is there And In short, they are going to fight to die in
там А Они короче идут воевать умирать в
Ukraine for  some kind of ldnr
Украину за какой-то лднр
lnr In short, it’s just
лнр Короче просто
cruel, you stupidly can’t figure out the
жесть вы тупо не можете разобраться со с
rights of Russians, stupidly in Russia, yes, you’re like this In
правами русских тупо в России да вы этом
short,
как Короче у
Putin’s, but look how remarkable Yes, that’s
Путина но смотрите как примечательно Да
who is watching from the different peoples of the
вот кто у нас смотрит из разных народов
Russian Federation What kind of thinking are
Российской Федерации Какое мышление вот
these all these Russian imperials Yes  they want
этих всех русских имперцев Да они хотят
Tatarstan to be part of Russia
чтобы Татарстан был в составе России
Yakutia they want it all to be
Якутия они хотят чтобы это всё было в
part of Russia so that they control it all and
составе России чтобы они это всё
receive resources but in
контролировали получали ресурсы но чтоб
short These people came to Moscow for
короче Эти люди Приезжали в Москву
nothing  It’s them, Damn, from Dagestan they’re climbing
не Чего это они Блин Из Дагестана лезут
into Moscow, they want to build a mosque. That is, you
в Москву мечеть хотят строить То есть вы
can there in Sochi, in short, damn it, come
можете там в Сочи короче блин приезжать
to the lands of the Circassians there, and like to the Caucasus
на земли там черкесов да типа на Кавказ
there, and to Dagestan, to all these lands,
там и на дагестанский на все эти земли
you can, yes, as you want, yes And when they
это можете да вы как хотите да А когда к
come to you, you  such that it's there
вам приезжают вы такие что это там
These came in large numbers Yes because
Понаехали эти Да потому что
this one is Russian Imperial such a
этот как оно российский Имперский такой
concept yes It is built on the hostility of all
концепт да Он построен на неприязни всех
these peoples they consider peoples
этих народов они считают народы
second-rate Yes, and the metropolis
второсортный Да а метрополия
Moscow, and even Moscow You see, they don’t
Москва причём даже Москва Видишь не
consider some other regions, they
считают какие-то другие области вот у
have Moscow. This is for them like
них есть Москва Вот это для них типа
Russia, write nay Telegram directly at once axis
Россия пиши най Telegram прям зараз ось
VN
ВН
AK more and more respectfully YouTube Zaga
АК це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through srg or in new ban and  I
нас через срг ор в ньй бан и дуже багато
don’t show too many videos to people at any time I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показу
information about streams That’s why
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
I need to  Mali operational link is written
ми Мали оперативний звязок пишиться
directly at once and while there in telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video Tsikava and Korisna information and we are
видео цикава и корисна информация и мы
sorry for you trimati postiyny
повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link is
оперативный звязок
independent in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write E
пиши E